eazework.com 2018-03-17

# Privacy and Security Policy

##  Last Updated : 20th August 2014

## Information Collected

“Personal Information” means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, telephone number a home, postal or other physical address, birth date, gender, occupation. When you choose to pay online for our applications and services you also have to provide your credit card or bank account information but we never store that information.  
When you are given a user account you can create a login id and password that is known only to you. We will never ask you for your password and strongly discourage sharing of this information with anyone. 

## Data Ownership

As you use our application you will update information on your company, customers, processes, financial information, product information etc. All such information uploaded through your login id remains your sole and exclusive property. This information is also classified as Personal Information. Please note that the usage of EazeWork applications and services is governed by our Terms of Service. 

##  Cookies and Tracking Technology

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only Personal Information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies save you time, for example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a website; a cookie recalls your specific information on subsequent visits.

EazeWork website also uses cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. You may accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, however you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies.

As you navigate through www.eazework.com, certain anonymous information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, clickstream). Your internet browser automatically transmits to this site some of this anonymous information, such as the URL of the web site you just came from and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using; the date and time you access the site and the pages that you access while at the site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and administer the site. This site may also collect anonymous information from your computer through cookies and internet tags or web beacons. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this site might not work without cookies. 

## Google Analytics and Google Adwords

In addition to cookies, our site uses Google Analytics which also uses cookies. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.   
Third party vendors, including Google, can show your ads on sites on the internet which are based on a your prior visits to our website. 

This website uses the [Google Adwords](http://www.google.com/ads/adwords) remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven't completed a task on our site, for example signing up for a trial of EazeWork product. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the [Google Display Network](http://www.google.com/ads/displaynetwork). Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the Tradevine website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), or if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or [permanently using a browser plugin](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Only authorized EazeWork employees with complete training in security and privacy processes and under managerial supervision will have access to your Personal Information. Primarily this access is needed to provide customer service and resolve application performance or system issues.

At times EazeWork will use third party vendors and we may need to transfer your Personal Information to them. In all such cases only the relevant information will be transferred to them and they will also be compulsorily required to follow our Privacy and Security Policy.

We may transfer your Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to -  
a) conform to the edicts of law or comply with legal process served on EazeWork  
b) protect and defend the rights or property of EazeWork, or  
c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of EazeWork’s employees, users of EazeWork’s products or services, or members of the public.

##  How We Use Information Collected

The information collected is used by us to set up the services for our users and their organizations. In addition, we may also use the information to contact you for discussions regarding our applications or the services we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. We will also be using the email address to send information regarding updates to the applications and services or company news, and a email newsletter. Additionally, we also ask customers to provide an email address while registering for the services, in order to send a username and password.

You will have the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of receiving communications from EazeWork when you elect to use our software product on a free-trial basis, or purchase / upgrade an account. Further, when you receive the requested communication, you are given the opportunity to unsubscribe from receiving any future communication or to change your information.

##  Data Security

At EazeWork, protection of customer data and applications is of highest priority. We take all precautions to keep your data safe and secure. The platform is hosted at the state of the art data centre, using the latest firewall protection, intrusion detection systems, SSL encryption and proprietary security products and managed by a team of experts to keep customer data stored in a high security facility where even physical access is audited and controlled. All data is regularly backed up to ensure that your data is never lost, even in the worst of calamities.

EazeWork provides a unique user name and password to each user that must be entered each time a User logs on. A session "cookie" is issued only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of a specific session. The session "cookie" does not store either the username or password of the user or any other confidential user and session information, but instead implements more advanced security methods based on dynamic data and encoded session IDs. In addition, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects your information using both server authentication and data encryption while accessing our site using Latest two versions of Google Chrome, Microsoft Internet Explorer, Safari and Mozilla Firefox.

Questions regarding the security practices of the Services should be emailed to [vaibhav@eazework.com](mailto:vaibhav@eazework.com).

##  Data Backup

We backup data every eight hours and keep it at a different location from the primary data center to provide back and redundancy in case of a failure at the primary location.

##  Changes to this Security and Privacy Policy

EazeWork may amend this policy from time to time, the amended policy will be posted at the same link as it is posted now. It is the responsibility of users to ensure that they periodically visit this link to read the updated policy. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Personal Information we will make that information available by posting a notice on [www.eazework.com](http://www.eazework.com/ "www.eazework.com") site.

##  Contact Information

EazeWork welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that EazeWork has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact EazeWork by email at [vaibhav@eazework.com](mailto:vaibhav@eazework.com), and we will promptly address the issue.
